Guide to the Historical Planning publications collection, 1888-2002.
Historical Planning publications collection
- Series XXXV. Urban Renewal
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Maine, 1946-1952 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Maryland (1), 1950 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Maryland (2), 1950 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Massachusetts (1), 1952 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Massachusetts (2), 1962-1972 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Minnesota, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Missouri, 1951-1966 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - New Hampshire, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - New Jersey, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - New York (1), 1940-1953 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - New York (2), 1956-1959 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - New York (3), 1960-1966 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - North Carolina, 1961-1969 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Ohio, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Ohio - Cleveland (1), 1951-1957 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Ohio - Cleveland (2), 1959-1961 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Ohio - Dayton, 1952 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Ohio - Dayton (Oversized), 1961 (Box 62)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Ohio (Oversized), 1946 (Box 70)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Pennsylvania, 1952-1965 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Pennsylvania - Philadelphia (1), 1947-1951 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Pennsylvania - Philadelphia (2), 1955-1967 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Pennsylvania - Philadelphia (3), 1967-1968 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Pennsylvania (Oversized) (Box 61)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Pennsylvania - Bethlehem (Oversized), 1956 (Box 70)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Pennsylvania - Philadelphia (Oversized), 1955 (Box 69)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Rhode Island, 1949-1953 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Tennessee, 1947-1968 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Virginia, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - West Virginia, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Wisconsin, 1949-1959 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Foreign - Canada (1), 1952-1954 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Foreign - Canada (2), 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Foreign - Japan, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Foreign - Netherlands, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal - Redevelopment - Foreign - Spain, 1945 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - General, 1945-1961 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Arkansas (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Colorado (1), 1956 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Colorado (2) (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Connecticut, 1957-1965 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - District of Columbia (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Illinois, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Maine, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Maryland, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Massachusetts, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Missouri, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - New York State, 1954-1967 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Pennsylvania, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - South Carolina, 19 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Foreign - Great Britain, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Urban Renewal - Rehabilitation - Foreign - Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - General, 1950-1960 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Arkansas (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - California (1) (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - California (2) (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Colorado, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Connecticut (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - District of Columbia (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Illinois, 1950-1960 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Massachusetts, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Michigan, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Minneapolis, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Minneapolis, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Missouri, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S., 1966 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Arkansas, 1956-1965 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - California (1), 1955-1957 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - California (2), 1958-1962 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Colorado, 1954-1960 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Connecticut, 1955-1963 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - District of Columbia, 1957-1968 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Florida, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Georgia, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Hawaii, 1966-1967 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Illinois (1), 1960-1964 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Illinois (2), 1963 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Kansas, 1959-1962 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Maryland, 1956-1965 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1959-1967 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Michigan, 1944-1964 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Missouri, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - New Hampshire, 1957-1959 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - New Jersey, 1958-1965 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - New York (1), 1957-1958 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - New York (2), 1960-1967 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - North Carolina, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Ohio (1), 1956-1958 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Ohio (2), 1959-1962 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Oregon, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1954-1962 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Rhose Island, 1953-1970 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Tennessee, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Texas, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - U.S. - Virginia (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Georgia, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Honolulu, Hawaii, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Illinois, 1953-1957 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Indiana, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Kansas, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Kentucky, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Maine, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Maryland, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Massachusetts, 1955-1962 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Michigan, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Minnesota, 1954-1957 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Missouri, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Nevada, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - New Hampshire, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - New Jersey (1), 1955-1959 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - New Jersey (2), 1955-1961 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - New York, 1955-1965 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Ohio, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Pennsylvania, 1955-1961 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Rhode Island, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Tennessee, 1955-1957 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Texas, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Utah, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Virginia, 1951-1955 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Washington State, 1957-1960 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Wisconsin, 1956-1962 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - NYC, New York, 1933-1959 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - NYC, New York, 1956-1959 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Greensboro, NC (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Pennsylvania, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Philadelphia, PA, 1952-1959 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Vermont, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Urban Renewal - Relocation - Great Britain, 1956-1959 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Urban Renewal - Universities, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - General, 1956-1962 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Alabama, 19 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Alaska, 1955-1956 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Arkansas, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - California (1), 1955-1963 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - California (2), 1955-1960 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Colorado, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Delaware, 1955-1956 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Urban Renewal - Workable Programs - Washington, D. C., 1955-1956 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Series XXXVI. Water
  - Water - General, 1950-1960 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Water - General, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Water - General, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Water - General, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Water - U.S, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Water - U.S, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Water - U.S. - Arkansas, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Water - U.S. - California, 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Water - U.S. - California, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Water - U.S. - Chesapeake Basin (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Water - U.S. - Colorado, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Water - U.S. - Colorado River, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Water - U.S. - Columbia River, 1940,1960 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Water - U.S. - Delaware River Basin, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Water - U.S. - Delaware River Basin, 1940-1950 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Water - U.S. - Delaware River Basin, 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Water - U.S. - Delaware River Basin, 1930-1950 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Water - U.S. - Delaware River Basin, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Water - U.S. - District of Columbia, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Water - U.S. - Florida, 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Water - U.S. - Florida, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Water - U.S. - Great Lakes Region, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Water - U.S. - Illinois (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Water - U.S. - Indiana, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Water - U.S. - Iowa, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Water - U.S. - Kansas, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Water - U.S. - Maine, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Water - U.S. - Maryland, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Water - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Water - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Water - U.S. - Michigan, 1940-1960 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Water - U.S. - Missouri River Basin, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Water - U.S. - New Jersey, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Water - U.S. - New Mexico (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Water - U.S. - Rhode Island (1), 1952-1966 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Water - U.S. - Rhode Island (2), 1956-63 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Water - U.S. - Rhode Island (3), 1945-1961 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Water - U.S. - Rhode Island (4), 1948-1964 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Water - U.S. - Rhode Island (5), 1959-1961 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Water - U.S. - Rhode Island (6), 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Water - U.S. - Sacramento River, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Water - U.S. - St. Lawrence River, 1940-1941 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Water - U.S. - Tennessee (1), 1936-1965 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Water - U.S. - Tennessee (2), 1959-1965 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Water - U.S. - Virginia, 1959-1967 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Water - U.S. - NYC, New York, 1916-1965 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Water - U.S. - New York State (1), 1934-1936 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Water - U.S. - New York State (2), 1937-1967 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Water - U.S. - New York State (3), 1936-1949 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Water - U.S. - New York State (4), 1958-1968 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Water - U.S. - New York State (5), 1935 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Water - U.S. - New York State (6), 1935 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Water - U.S. - New York State (7), 1965-1969 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Water - U.S. - North Dakota, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Water - U.S. - Ohio, 1943-1962 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Water - U.S. - Ohio River Valley, 1936 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Water - U.S. - Pennsylvania (1), 1937-1946 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Water - U.S. - Pennsvylania (2), 1962 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Water - U.S. - Potomac River, 1950-1966 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Water - Waterfronts - New York - N.Y.C., 1928-1961 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Water - Waterfronts - New York - N.Y.C. (Oversized) (Box 61)
  - Water - Waterfronts - New York - Buffalo, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Water - Waterfronts - California, 1959-1962 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Delaware River (1), 1952-1957 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Delaware River (2), 1958-1963 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Delaware River (3), 1964-1968 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Washington, D.C., 1929-1931 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Georgia, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Water - Waterfronts - General, 1929-1967 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Great Lakes, 1959-1968 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Louisiana, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Maryland, 1955-1957 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Michigan, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Missouri, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Water - Waterfronts - New Hampshire, 1947-1958 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Water - Waterfronts - New Jersey, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Ohio, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Water - Waterfronts - San Francisco Bay, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Tennessee, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Virginia, 1931-1966 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Wisconsin, 1920-1967 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Sydney and Newcastle, Australia, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Winnipeg, Canada, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Water - Waterfronts - Republic of Dahomey, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Water - Flood Control - General (1), 1952-1965 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Water - Flood Control - General (2), 1936 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Water - Flood Control - General (3), 1941-1961 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Water - Flood Control - Alabama, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Water - Flood Control - California, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Water - Flood Control - California (Oversized), 1956 (Box 62)
  - Water - Flood Control - Columbia River (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Water - Flood Control - Connecticut, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Water - Flood Control - Illinois, 1959-1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Water - Flood Control - Kansas, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Water - Flood Control - Kentucky, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Water - Flood Control - Michigan, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Water - Flood Control - Nebraska, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Water - Flood Control - New England, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Water - Flood Control - New York State, 1935-1948 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Water - Flood Control - Ohio, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Water - Flood Control - Rhode Island, 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Water - Flood Control - Tennessee (1), 1956-1960 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Water - Flood Control - Tennessee (2), 1956-1960 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Water - Flood Control - Tennessee-Virginia (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Water - Flood Control - Egypt (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Water - Laws, 1954-1966 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Water - General, 1935-1969 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Water - States, 1935-1968 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Series XXXVII. Zoning
  - Zoning - Aesthetics (1), 1949-1962 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Zoning - Aesthetics (2), 1949-1962 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Zoning - Aesthetics (3), 1949-1962 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Zoning - Aesthetics (4), 1949-1962 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Zoning - General (1), 1920-1967 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Zoning - General (2), 1920-1967 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Zoning - General (3), 1920-1967 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Zoning - General (4), 1920-1967 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Zoning - General (5), 1920-1967 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Zoning - General (6), 1920-1967 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Zoning - Sample Rezoning Case File, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Zoning - U.S. - California, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Zoning - Administration - General, 1955-1959 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Zoning - Administration - Arkansas, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Zoning - Administration - California, 1947-1964 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Zoning - Administration - Colorado, 1926-1958 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Zoning - Administration - Indiana, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Zoning - Administration - Illinois, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Zoning - Administration - Massachusetts, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Zoning - Administration - New York, 1948-1957 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Zoning - Administration - Ohio, 1923-1941 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Zoning - Administration - Texas, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Zoning - Building Laws, 1920-1970 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Zoning - Laws and Ordinances - Colorado (Oversized), 1954 (Box 61)
  - Zoning - Laws and Ordinances - Georgia (Oversized), 1955 (Box 61)
  - Zoning - Laws and Ordinances - Illinois (Oversized), 1954 (Box 61)
  - Zoning - Laws and Ordinances - Maryland (Oversized), 1952 (Box 61)
  - Zoning - Laws and Ordinances - New Jersey (Oversized), 1922 (Box 61)
- Series XXXVIII. Other
  - Architecture - Croatia (1) (Oversized), 1957-1959 (Box 71)
  - Architecture - Croatia (2) (Oversized), 1960 (Box 71)
  - Bridges - Pennsylvania (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Business Districts - Traffic - Illinois - Chicago (Oversized), 1950 (Box 70)
  - Business Districts - U.S. - Alabama - Mobile (Oversized), 1967 (Box 70)
  - Business Districts - U.S. - Alabama - Mobile (Oversized), 196? (Box 62)
  - Business Districts - U.S. - Ohio - Oberlin (Oversized), 19 (Box 70)
  - Capital Improvements - Idaho (Oversized), 1940 (Box 69)
  - Capital Improvements - Tennessee (Oversized), 1961 (Box 69)
  - Civic Centers - U.S. - New York - New York City (Oversized), 1948 (Box 71)
  - Counties - California - Riverside (Oversized), 1960 (Box 71)
  - Counties - New Jersey (Oversized), 195? (Box 69)
  - Counties - Plans - New Jersey (Oversized), 1964 (Box 62)
  - Counties - Tennessee - Davidson (Oversized), 1960 (Box 69)
  - Design Factors - Minnesota - St. Paul (Oversized), 1967 (Box 70)
  - Economic Factors - U.S. (Oversized), 1950 (Box 62)
  - Employment - U.S. - Pennsylvania (Oversized), 1959 (Box 69)
  - Maps - General, 1940-1957 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Maps - Ariel Photography, 1937-1958 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Maps - Foreign - Puerto Rico (Oversized) (Box 70)
  - Model Cities - General (1), 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Model Cities - General (2), 1969 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Model Cities U.S. - Illinois, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Model Cities U.S. - New York, 1967-1969 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Open Space - General (1), 1956-1960 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Open Space - General (2), 1961-1969 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Open Space - U.S. - Colorado, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Open Space - U.S. - New York - Westchester Co. (Oversized), 1965 (Box 69)
  - Open Space - Foreign - Canada (Oversized), 1961 (Box 70)
  - Poverty - Poverty, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Peace - Research, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Pedestrian - U.S. - California, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Preliminary Planning Research - Data - Tokyo Development (Oversized) (Box 61)
  - Planners - Planners (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Poverty - Poverty, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Poverty - Poverty, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Poverty - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Public Relations - Public Relations, 1940-1950 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Public Relations - Public Relations, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Public Relations - Public Relations, 1910,1930 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Public Relations - Public Relations (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Regions - Virginia (Oversized), 1956 (Box 61)
  - Regions - Plans - Indiana (Oversized), 1956 (Box 61)
  - Reuse of Refuse - Disposal, 1960-1970 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Reuse of Refuse - Disposal, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Rural Planning - Foreign, 1959-1967 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Rural Planning - Foreign - Malaya (Oversized), 1962 (Box 61)
  - Rural Planning - Foreign - Malaya (Oversized) (Box 61)
  - Rural Planning - General (1), 1940-1960 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Rural Planning - General (2), 1963-1968 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Rural Planning - United States, 1932-1943 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Shores - General, 1942-1969 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Shores - California, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Shores - Michigan (1), 1958 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Shores - Michigan (2), 1958 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Shores - Michigan (3), 1958 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Shores - New York, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Shores - Rhode Island, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Soils - Conversation, 1936-1967 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Soils - Surveys - General, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Soils - Surveys - Massachusetts, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Soils - Surveys - New York, 1923-1969 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Soils - Surveys - Puerto Rico, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Soils - Surveys - Wisconsin, 1919 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Store Location - Maryland - Baltimore, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Store Location - Wisconsin - Milwaukee, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Suburbs - U.S. - Delaware, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Taxation - General (1), 1958-1960 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Taxation - General (2), 1961-1969 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Tourist Trade - U.S. - Florida, 1961-1968 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Tourist Trade - U.S. - Maryland, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Tourist Trade - U.S. - Virginia, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Universities and the City, 1969-1972 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Urban and Regional Aesthetics (1), 1947-1966 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Urban and Regional Aesthetics (2), 1966-1968 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Urban and Regional Aesthetics (3), 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Urban and Regional Aesthetics (Oversized), 1959 (Box 69)
  - Toronto Official Plan, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Prince George's County, MD Approved General Plan, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown, TX Century Plan, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 3)